nextjobathome.com 2013-11-26

# Next Job At Home Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes information that we, NGM may collect from you as part of the normal operation of our service and what may happen to the information we collect.

**Your Privacy is Important to Us**

Our Privacy Policy explains what information we obtain on the Site and how we use the information you disclose to us.

**Who We Are**

We are an online news reporting service that introduces persons such as yourself to Third Parties who have expressed a general willingness to review your information and determine if they are willing to provide you with the services or products that prompted you to visit our Site.

**Modification of Service and Termination / Unsubscribing (Opting Out)**

NGM at its sole discretion, for any or no reason, at any time without notice may decline use of their Service, and modify or discontinue temporarily or permanently their service. You agree that NGM without prior notice may immediately terminate or modify your access to their Newsletter or Service and that NGM will not be liable to you or any third party for any termination or modification of access to their newsletter or Service.

The Terms will continue to apply until terminated by either you or NGM by either notifying NGM at any time by contacting NGM by email or unsubscribing on the links attached in our emails to you; NGM has made both options available to you. Note you may unsubscribe at any time from the newsletter or offer emails, which must be done separately. You may also send us an email, and we will manually unsubscribe your email address from all of our files and mailings; please indicate if you wish to unsubscribe from the newsletter emails, offer emails or both.

NGM may at any time, terminate its legal agreement with you for any reason not limited to but including if you have breached any provision of the Terms, you act in a manner that indicates that you do not intend to, or are unable to comply with the provisions of the Terms, is required to do so by law, a subsidiary, affiliate, or partner with whom NGM offered the Services to you has terminated its relationship with NGM or you, NGM is no longer providing the Services to users in the country in which you are resident or from which you use the service or in NGM's opinion service is no longer commercially viable. Nothing in this Section shall affect NGM's rights regarding provisions of Services in the Terms above. When these Terms come to an end, all of the legal rights, obligations and liabilities that you and NGM have benefited from, been subject to which are expressed to continue indefinitely, shall be unaffected by this cessation, and the provisions herein and shall continue to apply to such rights, obligations and liabilities indefinitely.

To be removed from our list, simply click here now or on the unsubscribe links located on any of our emails. You can also reply to an email and request to be removed manually.

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect users' information. We cannot guarantee the security of your information against those who use advanced illegal means to breach and or hack our security defenses.

**Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy on the Site. Please see our terms of service, use and conditions. We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide - When you sign up for a NGM Account or other NGM service, or offer that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password).

Cookies - When you visit NGM, we may send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. NGM may also use cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including NGM sites that use our advertising cookies, and view or click on an ad supported by NGM's advertising services.

Log information - When you access NGM services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request with one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

User communications - When you send email or other communications to NGM, we may but are not required to retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

Affiliated NGM Services on other sites - We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to NGM in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites through which our services are offered may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

Third parties - NGM may make available third party applications through its services. The information collected by NGM when you enable other application is governed by their privacy policies.

Location data - NGM offers location-enabled services, and NGM may receive information about your actual location.

Links - NGM may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.

Other sites - This Privacy Policy applies to NGM services only. We do not exercise control over other site's or their respective links not owned by NGM from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you, which you accept full responsibility for using.

NGM only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and not limited to but including for the following purposes: Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising; Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; Protecting the rights or property of NGM or our users; and Developing new services.

Our privacy policy may be changed at anytime with no notice to you please check it daily for any changes.
